http://www.candt.org/privacy

Contact
Privacy noticeThe candt.org website is owned and operated by C&T. We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online and to this end have developed the following Privacy Policy to deal with issues which may concern you. Please read the Privacy Policy to understand how your personal information will be treated. This policy may change from time to time so please check it periodically.The privacy and security of your personal information is extremely important to C&T.  We are committed to protecting your personal information and being transparent about the information we hold.  This privacy policy explains how and why we use your personal data so that you can be confident about giving us your information.Please note that by sending us an email or leaving a voice message, it is assumed that you have read and agreed with this privacy notice.Who are we?We are Collar And Tie Limited and our working name is C&T.We are registered as a limited company, number: 2878790 and a registered charity, number: 1085653Our registered office address is: University of Worcester, Henwick Grove, Worcester, WR2 6AJWhat Personal Data do we collect?Your personal data (any information which identifies you, or which can be identified as relating to you personally for example, name, address, phone number, email address) will be collected and used by us. We’ll only collect the personal data that we need.Information you give us: When you make an enquiry by telephone or email, we will collect your personal data. This might include your name, email address and telephone number.Under 18?If you are under 18, please ensure that you have the permission of the person with parental responsibility before you provide us with your personal data.Why do we need your data?We need your basic personal data in order to be able to contact you about your C&T enquiry.How will we use your personal data?We will use your personal data to allow us to respond to any questions that you have about C&T.All your personal data will be processed by staff within our organisation.We have a data protection policy in place to ensure the effective and secure processing of your personal data.Will your personal data be shared with any third parties?C&T will not pass on your personal data to any third parties unless required to do so by the law or a regulatory authority. How long will we store your personal data?Your personal data will be held for as long as it takes us to deal with your enquiry and no longer than is reasonable and necessary.What are your rights?You have the right to ask if we have any personal data on you and to see that personal data; this is called a subject access request.  Subject access requests should be sent by email to info@candt.org or by post to The Data Protection Officer, Collar and Tie Limited, University of Worcester, Henwick Grove, Worcester, WR2 6AJ.Other WebsitesThere are links on our website to other websites that are not owned or managed by C&T.  We cannot be held responsible for the privacy of data collected by these websites.Changes to our privacy noticeWe regularly review our privacy notice and may need to make changes from time to time.  Any changes made will be posted on this page.ContactWe welcome any questions, comments or requests regarding this privacy notice.  We can be contacted at info@candt.org or at our registered office address.
C&T
University of Worcester, Henwick Grove,
Worcester, WR2 6AJ,
Collar & Tie Ltd, trading as C&T, is a company limited by guarantee registered in England and Wales number: 02878790 l
Registered charity number: 1085653
